Hello, everyone. Good evening.
It's almost the end of the year.
Today, our live stream theme is the production of underwear.
I am today's anchor, Tina.
The style that we are going to make today, I believe you have already seen it in our poster.
Let me show you again.
Let's take a look at this.
Let's take a look at this style.
This is the picture that you have just seen.
Today, we are going to make the bra for the upper body,
and the shorts and belted socks for the bottom.
Before we start the production,
I would like to tell you a little bit about the underwear production.
First of all, for the shape of the underwear in 3D,
currently, the entire industry for the production of 3D underwear
is mainly based on the appearance,
that is, the appearance of the design.
That is to say, if we have some companies in the production process
or in the development process,
we have to check the fit of the underwear,
and so on.
This area is currently limited.
Because of our underwear,
we know that many underwear has a certain shape.
But currently, the models in the entire industry are hard models.
So in this area,
it is not possible to show the shape of the underwear.
So for the entire underwear category,
we mainly look at the appearance of the underwear.
We mainly look at the appearance of the underwear.
Okay, let's start the production.
First of all,
we first lead a virtual model of Chloe in the software.
I lead Feifei here.
Because of some problems,
because of the live broadcast,
because of some problems,
the model's appearance in the entire process
is presented in the form of high-heels.
Otherwise, the live broadcast room may be separated.
So let's all forgive her.
Okay, then I'll give her a pair of white flat shoes.
Then we delete this shoe.
Let the model become a stooped state like this.
Then we can see that
actually, currently,
the model's size of the chest is relatively flat.
In order to have a better shape of the underwear,
we use the model's size adjustment function of Chloe.
Adjust the corresponding size of it.
You can also refer to my size to adjust it.
Now you can see that my chest is bigger,
and the whole thing has become wider.
So we switch to the advanced human body
to make its lower chest a little smaller,
so that its chest and lower chest have a relatively large gap.
In this case,
the whole chest shape will be more prominent.
Then we shorten the waist of the hind legs a little bit,
so that the problem of a little arching of the back
can be greatly improved.
It can also be adjusted to the chest.
Then we adjust the thigh,
knee and calf a little bit.
Adjust it a little bit.
It looks a little bit more coordinated.
Adjust the shoulder blades as well.
Adjust the shoulder blades a little bit,
because we have widened the chest.
The whole shoulder blade is too wide,
so it looks a little bit like a tiger's back and a bear's waist.
Then we insert the paper pattern of the underwear.
Like this underwear paper pattern,
you can also use this 3D model drawing function
to draw it and then extract it.
You can also do it in a 2D style.
First of all, based on this sample,
I will extract the steel ring of our bra.
I use the method of extracting here.
If you have a real steel ring in your hand,
you can also scan it
or take a picture of your steel ring.
Then based on the shape of the steel ring,
I will draw a steel ring board.
The sample width is about 8mm to 1cm.
Then I will build a fabric for it.
For the steel ring fabric,
we use Trim Hardware.
But pay attention to the strength of the gold tail gauze.
The value of the minimum tension must be adjusted.
To prevent it from stretching.
Then we use the positioning ball
to arrange the steel ring board
to the appropriate position.
But here you have to pay attention to this steel ring.
It is very difficult to just lock it
on the curve line below the chest.
Because as we said before,
the actual steel ring
can have a certain speed effect.
But our 3D model's chest is hard.
So you can only turn on the hardening
and use a fixed needle to try as hard as you can
to make the steel ring board
fit more evenly
on the curve line below the model's chest.
Then press W on the board
and add two fixed needles.
Here I just added a row of fixed needles
on both ends.
This way you can use the positioning ball
to easily control it and rotate it.
In short,
it is to make the steel ring board
fit more evenly and smoothly
on the curve line below the model's chest.
Here you have to adjust it a little bit.
Lift the side edge up a little bit.
When adjusting the steel ring,
you have to take into account
the shape of the steel ring
that you are currently making.
Some steel rings are almost equal in height
on the left and right.
The one I am making is low on the left and high on the right.
So when I am adjusting it,
you have to pay attention
to the shape of the steel ring
on the body.
The left side is lower and the right side is higher.
This way,
the shape of the steel ring
is the shape you want.
In fact,
one of the techniques made by Bra
is to make the steel ring first.
This is also one of the techniques.
Once we have set the position of the steel ring,
when making the shape of the steel ring,
it is relatively easy to make
a relatively full steel ring.
Here I grow these steel rings
to the drop side .
We put up here
this is the first screw,
we place one on each side,
is finally set to the drop side,
the surface is regular and high.
Then we are making the drop.
Once you put it on,
There will be some unevenness at the edge of the
surface of the image.
Click on the control key to draw a cup shape.
Then I will add a curve in the right-click to the line.
You can see the curve on the front.
Will this curve fit your needs?
Ok, you are done.
Thank you.
And then I drew a line in the middle of it, and the purpose of this line is to cut off the backlight, and then we will pick up the sample board and it will look like it can be made out of this amount of power.
Of course, what I'm doing here is a straight line. You can also draw a small section of the line up and down.
For example, the sample board that is extracted like this has two grooves. It depends on what kind of shape you want to make.
This is the method I'm going to show you today, which is to draw a line directly on the model to extract the sample board of its backlight.
If we have a friend who works directly in the factory, how can we extract the actual backlight into 3D?
You can find a sample of the actual backlight,
and then use scissors to cut a few holes on it, and then flatten it on the table so that you can press out its backlight.
Then you take a picture, and then go to the close, and then according to the outline of its backlight, you can outline this panel for him.
Okay, so now I'm going to give him this backlight.
For example, I'm going to reduce it to make it more delicate, and I just applied a backlight fabric to it.
I'll talk about this fabric later.
So how do you adjust the fabric?
I'll talk about it later.
And now I'm going to draw an 8mm wide inner line for him.
So I can go to his corner and cut it open.
After cutting it open, this position is used to sew my shoulder strap.
Now I'm going to use a fixed needle to fix it.
Now I'm going to adjust the physical properties of this backlight fabric.
Just now I used Trim Hardwear, but the backlight strength is relatively large, so it looks more rigid.
So now I've changed to a default fabric, which is the boss's default fabric.
That is, the backlight bend strength of his backlight is increased from 38 to 60, making it a little harder.
The advantage of using default fabric is that its backlight strength and backlight strength are not so great.
In this case, the fabric will be more smooth and not so stiff.
Okay.
I'm going to copy the other half of the other side and copy the corresponding one for him.
Note that I'm using this world coordinate all the time.
Ensure that my sample is leveled.
And then I'm going to take these samples from the bottom part of me and I'm going to take them out of the storage.
Okay.
And then arrange it for him.
And then I'll put this one in the back and I'll put it in the back.
Once you've arranged it, we'll just hook up the line in the corresponding square position and we'll merge the sample between them.
Note that we need to change the place where we made the outline and the outline of the area that needs to turn.
Don't forget to change it.
Then he.
so that the fold will be more even
Okay, let's continue to sew this piece
I will give it a name
Because there will be more fabric later
It won't be able to mix up later
Here, give it the name of the face
And then
I will use this
Trim Fusible Rigid
to give it a more solid shape
to prevent it from stretching
Because it is also
hard to stretch the back of the clothes
on the actual clothes
Okay, you can see
the back of the clothes
is not easy to stretch
Okay, you can see
the back of the clothes
is not easy to stretch
Okay, you can see
the back of the clothes
is not easy to stretch
So, here
we use the Trim Fusible Rigid
to give it a more solid shape
So, this curve will be more suitable
for the model's surface curve
Then find a relatively
flat position
a suitable height
to draw a
Trim Fusible Rigid
Now, we can put the back of the clothes on it
After drawing, we use
the Trim Fusible Rigid
to stick the tape
So, it will be able to
make the back of the clothes
flat
Now, I will
reduce the Trim Fusible Rigid
to 8
Because the sample here
is small
So, it will affect the simulation speed
Now, I will
start to make the strap
Now, I will start to make the strap
Open the Arrangement
and put it on the back
Then, I will
add a fabric
to the two straps
I will adjust the physical properties
of the strap
I will use the old-fashioned
fabric
The difference is that
the bending strength is a little harder
Then, I will
adjust the strength of the strap
Because it is not so easy to pull
But there is a certain stretching force
So, I adjust it a little
Then, the bending strength
will also be adjusted a little
The tail is not easy to pull
The gold is a little hard to bend
But the gold has a certain bending
So, the gold and the shoes
are a little softer than the tail
Because I mentioned earlier
This is just an appearance effect
The fitting of the bra
is not related to the
actual body of the clothes
So, we can adjust the
hand shape here
But, if we are doing other types of clothes
If you want to check the body shape
You must not adjust the hand shape yourself
Use the correct hand shape
Then, here
I found the position of the shoulder strap
If the position is wrong
It doesn't matter
We can adjust it
Here, I have a small detail
Adjust the bending strength
The bending strength of the shoulder strap
has been adjusted to zero
This can prevent my shoulder strap
from becoming thinner due to too much stretching
Pull it to the middle
When you pull it,
it is better to pull the inside
So that the shoulder strap does not turn
Then, I just moved it a little
Let it lean back
Then, I will
delete this
I just don't need it
I just delete it
Adjust the position of the shoulder strap
It looks smoother
It is not in the state of bending
The bending strength
Almost
It has always been called bending strength
So, in fact, all users
are already used to this name
The bending strength is that the bigger the bending strength
The more difficult it is to bend the fabric
The reaction will be harder
Then we continue to do it
The shoulder strap just now is a little tight
It's a little short, so I'll make this shoulder strap a little longer
I did too much just now
You can see the left side is twisted
So make it a little longer
If you are not long enough
You can extend it by one centimeter each time
Here, I put this
The 3D strength of the seam allowance
Adjust it to 0
Then look at this 3D in 3D
The seam allowance shadow
Can be hidden
Then here I will measure
This
The length of the inner strip
Then according to this length
I will draw two more long strips
After drawing these two long strips
This place svenges
So I will put it in
Short, 8mm
Because my frame is 8mm wide
Then make an intersection between the innerскую
add
Then it can be frenched
this
here
Here I choose to go directly to the frames
This way can prevent
There will be gaps between them
Well, if you sew here
and then the one below it
gives it a symmetrical spread
I'll sew it for him
I don't need to sew the other side again
Pay attention to the change of turn
Ok, reduce the number of these two small
adjusted panels to 5
The overall conflict thickness
is that I adjust the
conflict thickness of the entire bra
and then add it to the inside of this 3D
At this time, you can simulate it
I freeze my shoulder strap
in case there is a slide later
Then add it to the other side of the symmetrical spread
Ok, simulate it
Here I put mine
The overall of the inner strip
of the three pieces of the triangle
I turned it all over
Use the tool to adjust the strength
After turning it
Because I adjusted the property of the shoulder strap just now
So I just put it and the shoulder strap
together
I used one line
In this way
I need to turn it
The strength of its cervical line
can be applied to the correct line
Then I will deal with the back
The back buckle part
Here, in order to simulate
the real three-layer structure
I just gave it to him directly
I made three parts on average
Then give him a two-third
Then sew it up and add it to the outside
And then
I sewed the third one to the outside
And then I give him one more time
Then turn it
Then add this part to the outside
Ok, these three styles
Give him a new design
Correct fabrics
And then give him
The thickness of the conflict
And the thickness of theâu
Adjust more
The thickness of theâu
Make him a little thicker
I'm going to make the 3D hair line a little thicker.
I'm going to turn off the 3D hair line on the top and bottom.
So that it doesn't have that extra shadow.
It looks a little more normal.
Next, we're going to deal with the front.
I'm going to hook up the front.
Because it's a left-right symmetry, I'm going to draw an inner line in the center.
This way, I can hook up half of the hair.
I'm going to delete the unnecessary information.
I'm going to delete the inner line in the middle as well.
I'm going to open up the symmetry in the middle.
I'm going to sew it.
I'm going to make the back of the chest smaller.
I'm going to fill it in.
Next, I'm going to make the back of the chest smaller.
Pay attention to this part of the underwear.
Because it's not very big.
If you don't adjust the back of the chest,
The entire underwear will be very bone.
This detail doesn't look good.
Next, I'm going to add some related texture to it.
I'm going to use a little bit of this texture in the steel circle.
Adjust the size of the texture a little bit.
Because this texture is not made in 1 to 1.
And then we go down.
Give it the texture of the face.
Then here, I applied red to it.
Today we are making a red set.
Happy New Year in advance.
Then here, the shadow strength is strengthened.
The line strength is also opened.
Because this texture itself has a texture.
In order to make its texture clearer.
Then add the texture of this shoulder strap.
This shoulder strap is a bit of a flower.
You have to be more careful.
Find its contact.
It can be a Christmas set.
Of course, you can also make a New Year's set.
It's all red.
Give it this texture.
Then change the color.
Apply red to it.
The line strength.
The line sticker is opened.
Here you can check it in 3D.
The texture we just adjusted.
Next, give it the texture of the cup.
Change its color.
The shadow is a bit too strong.
Adjust the brightness of the shadow.
The shadow intensity is a little smaller.
It's not as strong as it should be.
Okay, let's give it another layer.
I'm going to apply this lace fabric to the outer layer.
You can also use a leather fabric.
and
This is the base.
add another layer
copy the face
and name it
lace1
later there will be many lace
make the texture smaller
it's a bit hard to see
make the hair line
bigger
make it smaller
remove the joint
make it left and right
again
I need to make the hair line
smaller
otherwise
the middle will be
a gap
it's not good
so I make it smaller
make it side to side
to avoid the gap
you can see
I want to adjust the texture
because the middle
has a thick red line
but it's not good
you need to freeze the steel
to use it for your model
it will transform later
and for the back of the neck, we will also use the velvet fabric
add a little bit of line drawing
yes, this is easy to do
you can try it out after watching the live stream
this is one of the core points of the bra
for example, you have finished the part of the shape
and you are satisfied with it
remember to freeze it
now, I will add the band to the bra
fix the band to the virtual model
so that it won't move during the simulation process
because we are going to make the details of the band
such as the slide and the ring
we have to simulate the band
in case it slides down, we have to fix it
for the back of the neck
I will make a ring structure
but for convenience
I will adjust it later
what we teach here today
is not to teach you how to make a real ring
but to teach you how to make a fake ring
a fake ring
I made a few internal lines here
and cut it
for the upper part
I am going to make a counter-fold structure
because we are going to make a ring
so I expanded the outside of the board
and made the internal line in the middle
adjust the corresponding seam line
because I am going to do a counter-fold later
now I am going to make a counter-fold
so I just adjusted the seam line
here is my counter-fold line
and my small board
the angle of the counter-fold line
you can adjust it yourself
don't need to fold it so tight
for example, 30 or 40 is ok
and here
this small board
we will adjust it later
I think that my small board
is stretched a little bit
it's obviously a little bit longer
than the second-hand ring
so I just made it a little bit longer
then I take my ribbon
and copy it here
and name it transparent
same physical comb
I just take this board
These two small panels are designed to be transparent, so it looks like there is no panel in the middle.
Adjust it a little bit to make the shoulder strap look smooth.
The transparent one in the middle is a little narrower.
Because if my ring is too wide, my ring will be made very large, which is not good.
Make it a little narrower.
Then I click on this triangle.
It's probably where I put this slide.
Add a inner line to the blue dot position on the 2D.
In this way, I'll hook it up.
This position is a reverse.
The slide needs to be reversed.
Take out this part of the reverse.
Adjust the principle a little bit.
Adjust the principle.
It was perfect.
It doesn't look like this.
Another reason why I want to see this,
the collapse of a space in the middle of green.
Then I'll hook up with hygiene.
It's a little narrower.
OK, this way is because the through.
Put this little chapter in the middle.
Be good.
In this way, it's not too much.
I'm going to make the window yellow
and leave some space for it
I'm going to lower it here
and we can adjust it later
Then, we turn the inner panel
to the outside
In this way,
I can adjust the angle
of the seam line
to about 30
Now, I can
move on to the next step
I'm going to draw a small
V-shape panel
This panel is going to be used
to install the panel
It's a 8-digit panel
Find the inner line
Then, make a border
on the inner line
and add the inner line
on both sides
You can make the V-shape
a little bit smaller
2 mm
Add the inner line
on both sides
The V-shape of the panel
is going to be like this
I didn't adjust it
I'm going to adjust it
a little bit
The V-shape continues to go down
because we can see
that it's not smooth
The V-shape is too big
I'm going to make it a little bit narrower
I'm going to make the panel
a little bit narrower
It's still a little bit uneven
So, I'm going to adjust the V-shape
to 1
You can see that there is a channel
in the middle
I'm going to copy this panel
and add it to the outside
Then, I'm going to model it
I'm going to add a circle
to the side of the panel
and add a 8-digit button
I'm going to add a 8-digit button
and put the 8-digit button
near the corresponding position
Then, I'm going to use the function
to adjust the size of the right upper corner
to make it a little bit smaller
I changed the coordinates
to the screen coordinates
because I personally prefer
the screen coordinates to be smoother
You can choose
to adjust the size
Then, I'm going to adjust the color
to red
Because this is a cloud trim file
I have already adjusted the material
before
If you do it yourself,
you can adjust it
But how to do this 8-digit button
You can use the cloud panel tool
to draw a 8-digit button
You can draw half of it
and then align it
Then, you can have a 8-digit button
You can draw a small circle
and then make a hole in the inner line
Then, use the round tool
to make the four corners a little bit rounder
Then, find one side
and align it
Then, you can have a 8-digit button
Adjust the position of the upper corner
delicately
On the other side
CTRL-C
Select Trim
CTRL-C, CTRL-V
Then, copy it on the other side
On the other side,
click on the shoulder strap
Then, adjust the position
You are so active
Then, add a ring
After the double-click,
use the glue to stick it
to the position
Adjust the color
Then, adjust the position
Now, I have
increased the gap
between the top and bottom
so that there are more gaps
in the middle
to allow me to place the small ring
Adjust it a little bit
It's like using a fake ring
I actually use a transparent plate
to fix my shoulder strap
In this way,
no matter when I simulate my bra
its structure must be very stable
If you want to do it in a real ring
you can also
After pressing Trim
you can open the gap
Then, you can use the gap
to make it
really in the middle
In this way,
you might be a bit not stable
when you are not careful
It depends on the method
you like
I am going to adjust the detail
I just simulated it
If there is a bump on the patch, the accessory will also have a certain position.
So after simulation, check and adjust a little more.
Now the shape of the whole piece of clothing is almost OK.
The details of the shoulder strap are OK.
Next, I will adjust the color of my backpack a little bit.
So that the lace on the outer layer looks a little bit more obvious.
Next, let's add some lace flowers to it.
On the upper layer of my bra,
the upper eye,
I will add some lace flowers.
Then, according to the size of the lace I want to add,
my width is 30 mm.
Then measure the size of the upper eye of my backpack,
and draw a G-shaped plate.
Then make a center line in the middle,
and sew it on my outer line,
on the upper eye line of the outer layer.
After sewing,
add it to the outside,
and then use this,
you can harden this plate,
and then support it to quickly simulate flatness.
Then make a 15 mm inner line border for it,
and divide my lower eye line and its inner line.
Now you can see that the layer of the lace in this position is a bit problematic.
Because our lace is a PNG picture,
it is a transparent picture.
The transparent channel shows that sometimes there will be a layer problem.
It doesn't matter.
I will give it a default fabric first,
to make it easier for me to see.
Anyway, I will add it at the end.
Finally, I will add the corresponding lace pattern to it.
Now you can see that the shape of the left and right sides
are not yet in line with the shape of my bra.
So I will adjust the angle of the line on both sides
according to this effect.
Pull the bottom point to the left
and hold the SHIFT key.
The right side is the same.
I will pull it to the right for the time being.
But I see that the length of this line
is different from the length on my top.
So I will do it in a different way later.
Now I am adjusting the length of the inner line on my bottom.
But in fact,
I will adjust it later.
I will make the upper eye a straight line.
It looks more beautiful.
And here,
there is a missing edge.
So I will do it again later.
So I am adjusting the length of this line
to the length of the inner line for the main line.
You can see that according to the trend of my back shop,
I added another inner line
on the shoulder strap.
And then according to the length of my inner line,
I will straighten this part.
The length of the inner line
I will extend the flower banks.
OK
adjust the seam allowance
the seam allowance is not correct
so delete it
then sew it again
pull it out
use the locator to pull it out
now I want to
fix the other side
stick it to my
the backrest
now I want to
want to fix this part
I adjust the length
so it's the same length
as the inside of my backrest
don't use too much bias
for the top
I also
stretch it out
it's missing, stretch it out
It seems to be a little short here, but it doesn't matter, because it is just the upper eye line, it is just a little short, it can wrap around my chest, so that the upper eye can be more flat, so it is just a little short, it's just right, and I just need to apply it directly to it.
Then add my lace flower edge to it on this plate, and name it lace 2.
Then adjust the direction of my lace flower edge. I use the upper right corner to adjust the direction of the pattern.
If the double arrow on the plate is the mark of the sand line, I am adjusting the direction of the pattern here.
Adjust it a little bit, the size of the lace edge.
I want to adjust the height of the lace flower edge directly under the pattern.
But when I adjust it, it doesn't fit well, so I will adjust it again.
I will adjust it again.
OK.
In this way,
I can adjust the size of the lace flower edge to the size I want.
OK.
With this kind of lace with transparency,
you can turn on the high-quality dye in the upper left corner of the three-dimensional window to check it out.
OK.
Then align it to the other side.
Select the plate and directly control D to align and copy it again.
Then it is also hard to simulate it.
You can pull it out a little bit and help it.
Wait a minute.
Or you can directly hard to use the positioning cue card to pull it out after the alignment is copied.
This way the simulation will be fast and flat.
I just deleted it.
It's okay to delete it.
You can see that the design is complete.
I just deleted it.
Now I'm almost done with the whole thing here.
Finally, let's look at the back and buckle position.
Free the entire bra.
Our back buckle position is actually one on the right side.
It is attached on the left side.
So I copied a plate out and made the buckle plate.
I extended it a little bit.
Make it a little bit longer
I deleted it
There is another way here
Expand with the outside of the board
Can I get the material?
For the material
Wait for our message on WeChat next week
Let me adjust it here
Can share with you
Good to continue down
I do the outside of the board here
Expand
Made two millimeters out
Then generate the internal line
Click to confirm
Then
The powder line here needs to be adjusted again
This is not necessary
Use this long to connect the left and right
Become this
Just created this small version
To connect my right side
After this simulation
It's not his
There will be a slight difference in the shape
Drink some water
I drink some Sprite
Cool
Then use that fake sewing needle here
Put my
This small version that was created just now
I just put these two panels on the level
Then use this fake sewing needle to put it
Measure the level for him
On the position of this internal line
Set each other
Just simulate our
The details of the metal square buckle
I didn't do the square buckle details on this model
Here, in fact, you can
Take a picture online
Find a picture online
Or take a picture on your phone
Take the texture of the square buckle
Take it out
Take it out separately
Then as a sticker
Just stick it up
This point is actually not difficult
Then here
Put this with the smooth
Form a smooth curve tool
Put my two feet
Make it into this corner
It looks more natural
All right
In this way
Our bra is done
You can take a look
It's done
Now I put this bra in the cold
Then give it to him
Use our
This
Storage function
In this way
In 3D
He will no longer occupy
The amount of your simulation
Then next
The part of my underwear
Give him
Remove the storage
Give him a new piece of cloth
Convenient for me to watch
Then match it
Need to
The part of the symmetrical copy
Give him a symmetrical copy
Out
The production of short pants is very simple
Also very fast
Then here
I put his
This
Two on the outer layer
This board
Level
Arranged a little
Use the positioning ball
Turned around
Use the blue scroll
Give him
Arranged the outer layer
But I just
Arrange
When I put it up with the arrangement point
I turned this
Angle
No
It doesn't matter
His layer is still
Not much effect
All right
Put it in the back
Then this piece
Small bottom of the board
I'm going to press 4
Come to the side
The side
Put it in the position of the bottom
You can switch to 0
To adjust it
Relatively this position
Let him
This is in the middle
I put mine now
This
Because now I
The board in the middle
It's not symmetrical
Then wait
Will cause me to sew twice
So I adjust it again
Delete the other half
Then align it
Then wait
All my operations
Just do half
It's more convenient
Cut off
Then delete the other side
Then align it
Open
It's all about
Editing board tools
Next
Use the sewing tool
Quickly
Give it to him
Sew it
Is just
The one on the belt
The inner line
Hook out
Then sew
Sew the side
Okay
This is also
Put it in the middle
Here is also the inner line
These two are symmetrical
Just hook one
Hook out
And then
Sew the inner line with the bottom
Okay
The other side corresponds to the balance
Balance is good
This short-stitch seam is very simple
I sewed one
It doesn't matter
Just cancel it
Make it up
The short-stitch seam is very fast
That can be seen
After the simulation
The shape is not very good
So let's put this
Z-stitch
Reduce to 5
Reduce the thickness to 1
Here
Then use the setting layer tool
Put this left side to the right
Set it
The left side is outside
In fact, it is the right belt of the model
But in this 2D
It looks like
Relatively left
That version
Then here
Put this
Slightly
Give him
Pull it
Let him
The position of this穿着
More suitable
But now we can see this
On the front side
See this
The corner of the foot
Is a little over-stretched
It's a little over-stretched
So now I choose
It's okay to move here
It's okay to cancel
Put this whole circle
Is the corner of the foot
Give him a choice
Hook the elasticity
Here you can see
The length of 2D and 3D
In fact, there is a big difference
It shows that this pants
Is pulled open
Normal underwear
Will be pulled open
So here
The proportion of elasticity
I said
110%
It is a certain amount of pull-out
But don't be pulled so much
Then this way
You can properly fix it
This corner
Let it
Better
Can have a
A round shape
Form
Then a little more
Pull it
At this time
If I pull it
You can see
It is very easy
Can pull this shape
Pull on the model
Because of this elasticity
There is a certain contraction force
Can be better
Go to
Grab the model
Next
I will hide the model
Look at the bottom
The position
Give him
A little more
It's okay
The bottom position
Give him
A layer inside
The layer inside
I will first
This
The elasticity of the bottom
Turn off
Because it's a little bit
Pulled too hard
It bulged in the middle
This shape is not very good
So give it a little bit
Adjusted
it
is
with
here
big
This shape
Same
بة
And then
How to do
I did everything
In these
Hold down
hold down
I will
might
wait
The length is measured just now
Then quickly sew it with my little back
Also sew the top and bottom
Reduce the width of this plate
Reduce the thickness of the window
Then harden and add to the outer layer
simulation
At this time, I will pull this down a little bit
You can see that this shape is better
It is more flat to wrap your thigh
The whole shape will be more smooth
It's more comfortable to look at
Add to the outer layer here
Harden and simulate
Because there are two layers of bottom
See him fighting
It doesn't matter
Just set it with this setting layer
Pull it out a little bit
Now you can see it on both sides
There is such a better shape
Wrap my thigh
At this time, I will add my bottom
Add this elasticity
It looks like it
It will be more normal
it is good
Now I will designate my corresponding fabric
Give it the corresponding position
The front and the back
These two pieces are for him
Make a column layer inside
Simulate
The column layer inside
Inside that layer
Use this
Face and skin
The lace fabric outside
Change it to my bra
The fabric is the same
So that the upper and lower layers
This feeling will be better
Then
Set up a lace 2
Designate the corner for me
I want to make the two corners of the corner
Make a lace edge
Then this is for him
I dropped it
Because I think one side
His lace side is big
The other side is small
I want to use the small side
The denser side
It looks better
A little bit
Here, I use this
I opened this high-quality rendering
See
The layer here is a bit problematic
So use the layer setting tool
Put mine
The lace and my cross belt
Set it up for him
Need to distinguish left and right
Simulate
That's it
Put this red fabric
Set the transparency to 80%
It looks more
More layered
Then put my short cloth
Short action
Next
We are going to make the part of the lace
Add a new fabric
Then I want to
Is to let the lace
How high to wear
I'm in that position
Draw two
Draw a circle
Psychological explanation
Then use the editor
Right click
You can generate a symmetrical
Psychological explanation
Psychological model explanation
I choose him
See him
The whole circle is about
More than 500 mm
Then I
This silk hair
Must be narrower than him
A little bit
The idea of ​​making this silk hair
Is to make one first
Wider version
Now
Why
You
Will
Slip
Ah
There are two possibilities
One possibility is that your shoulder
The shoulder strap is too short
It's too short
The force is stronger
It will slide down
There is another one
Is that your shoulder strap is too loose
It will slide down
But how to say
Sometimes the shoulder strap
In the simulation process
There is indeed a chance of sliding down
So in the previous one
This
In the demonstration process
There is a point to be mentioned
Is to use that fake needle
Fake needle
Use a fake needle tool
On your shoulder strap
Write it down
Write it down on your virtual model
In this way, you can put your shoulder strap
Fixed on the virtual model
On
Then you
One point
Fixed
It won't slide down
How much is the size of the product
Wait a minute
Let me show you
Let me show you at the end of the live broadcast
Continue down
Just that
Let's talk about this today
A logic of the production of silk hair
Because
We know that the actual silk scarf
Its
A circle is very small
Then it's
Very flexible
Can be
Pulled up
But you need to pay attention
We are in the free
Let's
We need to
Make the board wrap the model
Let's
The board
Simplify into clothing
If you
When you first make it
The board is very narrow
You can't
Wrap it very well
The shape of the leg
So what we are thinking about today
Is to create a relatively wide board first
The size of the leg
so that it can better wrap around the model's legs.
After shaping, sew it into a bucket,
and then simulate it on the model, and then slowly adjust it.
This is our core idea today.
Continue down.
Okay, now I just made a mistake.
The length is a little too long, so I adjusted it.
Then put it on the arrangement point,
adjust its direction with the positioning ball,
so that it can better follow the trend of the legs to wrap.
You can see that the sewing line on the side
needs to be wrapped around my legs
so that it won't fall off.
Okay, just now, I used this
stick-on sewing model band function
to stick the upper line and the band together.
Now I will increase the diameter of this
and then use the positioning ball.
You can turn this hole.
Then you can also move it
so that it can wrap around your legs.
Next, we have to find a way
to make it tighten the board piece step by step.
After using the adjustment board tool
to select the board piece,
double click on the center point.
After all the points turn yellow,
then adjust it to the side.
This is the end of the shrink.
It can be better,
it can be realized,
that is, the two sides are closed at the same time.
In this way, it won't cause you this.
This can ensure that your opening
is always on the inside of the thigh.
If you don't use this,
don't activate this center point,
and just shrink it,
it is a single-sided shrink.
When you simulate it later,
it may cause your opening and closing
to appear forward or backward.
Then you need to spend your energy
to pull this opening line
to the inside of your thigh.
This is a bit of a backstroke.
So this is why I used
the center point of activation just now
to shrink both sides at the same time.
Continue down.
Then now in this position,
the corner of the foot,
in order to simulate it,
I first removed the pin needle of the corner of the foot.
Now I need to add the pin needle
in this relatively inside position
and simulate it again,
so that the corner of the foot looks more natural.
Continue the same way.
Activate the center point,
shrink both sides inward at the same time.
Add a circle of pin needle to the corner of the foot.
Add a point to the center point.
I want to sew it up now,
see if it works.
Just go in.
I just added the center point,
sew it left and right,
and then simulate it.
It pierced through my toes.
It doesn't matter.
Just put the pin needle
on the bottom of this piece,
and then pull it out with the pin needle.
Now I put the pin needle in the middle of my socks.
Pull it down.
I feel that my socks
are a little tight.
It doesn't matter.
Activate the center point,
continue to shrink it.
And then I will fix it in front.
If you don't,
it will probably run away.
At this time,
reduce the example building to 5.
Just now it will go through
because our example building is too big.
So it will go through.
The front position is a little crooked.
So I added a circle of pin needle
and turned it around.
Turn it around a little.
OK.
Next,
I use the survival round to fix it.
I just made it a little bit.
OK.
It's a little bit.
Then I will add the bars on the back.
This is an elevator tool.
Lock the wire.
Then, the 12 of the line
are all the length of 50.
This center point is also
increased by 50 in the center.
Then use the conjure tool
to adjust its languages.
If that's the case,
I want to finish this.
Next, I put thisgado line.
It's a little crooked.
It's okay.
I'm going to adjust it
I'm going to adjust the embossing line
Use the edge embossing tool to move it to the corresponding straight line point
Then turn off the embossing strength
Because I don't want it to have this mark on the inside
The symmetry is on the other side
Come to the front
Because I am now on the front left of the screen
Turn the screen to the right
Then put the upper eye line on the elastic band
Use the elastic band tool
Then it's not very tight now
So I choose these two socks
Tighten the end-to-end shrink rate
Adjust the end-to-end shrink rate to 90 and tighten it again
Tighten it again to 80
I think it's tight enough to stick to my socks
Let me tell you here
Why?
Just now I didn't use it directly
Isn't our board very wide at the beginning?
Then why didn't you use the wide board directly to add the shrink rate?
Because we know that the shrink rate is through shrinking your grid
It's just the interval between particles and particles to shrink your board
If your sample is wider
It means that the number of grid on your sample board is very large
At this time, you need to add a very large shrink rate
For example, 20%
Then you can shrink it into a sock shape
But in that state
There are still a lot of particles in your socks
After shrinking, it will cause the distance between your particles and your particles to be very close
Then when you simulate
There may be some instability
Maybe your socks will shake when you simulate
So if you don't understand
You'll understand when you try it back
So try to adjust the sample board
Adjust it to the actual size of your socks
There's a little bit of space left
It's not very big
There's a little bit left
When you don't meet the shrink rate
You add a little shrink
There is no big problem at this time
It won't happen
This kind of dynamic instability
Now let's use the grid to check
Okay, next
I'm going to do it for him
The internal line diameter
Is needed to cut out
This part of the lace that I'm playing
The internal line here is used to cut and trim
Adjust it a little bit
See if you can pull it up
It doesn't matter if you can't pull it up
Because my socks may be shorter
Yes, the socks are used to ink the fabric
Because you don't need to give him a special fabric here
But the front of the socks may be faster
It's the socks
I have a little adjustment in front of me
It's inked
But I put it
The strength of the gold and the strength of the tail
It's about 10
It's basically 10 to 15
Just make it a little bit smaller
Because the socks are easy to pull
So you can adjust the gold and the tail a little bit
And then I feel it's too wide
So I'm going to make it a little bit narrower
The part of the socks is almost there
Next I'm going to make this waist
It's his waist
The belt of the socks on the waist
What about this belt
I just made a size
You can use this size
According to
If you are experienced
Maybe you can just type out this size
If you're not sure
It doesn't matter
Just draw a shape
I did half of it
So it can be symmetrical
Now you can see that I made it shorter
I'm going to use this adjustment sheet to widen it
A little wider
I added it before and after
At this time you can see it's a little bit of a problem
Add a little less
Then
I just made a mistake
Select the front piece separately
To move
If you
Move together
There will be a problem
Pull it back and forth
Make it wider
Because he always runs up
It's not good to run up
Come down a little bit
I hope he can just be stuck
I want him to stay in that position
Make it a little bit narrower
OK
Then there will be a little bit of space
I can use this one
Now I'm going to use the tool
To apply it to this tape
Hardening
The force of the force is reduced
The impact is reduced
Harden
Rewind
The bottom line is a bit uneven
So I'll draw a tape for it
And paste it
Now it's going to stick to it
It will be a little bit
It's going to be a little bit
I think it's a little bit
The effect is a little bit
You can see it's not too much
It's a little bit
The effect is a little bit
we will need to remove it again
Okay, then
Next, we are going to create the strap between the belt and the socks
In 3D, I have marked the position of the blue dot
It's probably in this position
What I am using now is the tool to add a knife
I added a knife to this corresponding position
Then right-click on the cutout to add a line
The width of this knife is 30
That's the width of the bag I'm going to make later
Then here on this sock
I also marked it
Just click on 3D
Then on the sock
I used the knife tool to add this 30 knife
But here I ignored a problem
In fact, there is no need to draw a knife here
If you draw it, you can't use it later
It's useless
Because our socks are pulled very hard
So you can't sew according to the width of 30
You can see it later
Okay, here I draw according to the approximate length
I drew a straight strap
Sew it
After sewing, you can see that the length of the sewing line is wrong
Because in fact, the bottom plate was pulled
So here I used this
I deleted this cutout
It's useless
Use the edge sewing line tool to shorten my sewing line
How long to adjust
I will see
Here I want to simulate
Before this
I will re-stick my socks
Because I added a knife and a dot to the top line just now
It means that the nature of this line has been changed
So re-stick it
Then after simulation
Adjust the length of this bag
I put the bottom line
Because of the relationship of adding a knife
It also automatically removes the adhesion of the tape
The problem is not big
Then add a circle of sewing needle to the top line
Prevent it from sliding
Here
The adhesive that has been removed from the top
Here I will add the adhesion
It's just right
Because I need it to have a bag
The effect of pulling out
So I also need to remove the adhesion of the belt
Then I will sew the other side in the corresponding position
On the other side
It's the other one
After the adhesion of the belt is copied
You can see its position
In fact, the left and right are a little asymmetric
It's a little slanted to the left
So here I re-drawn a tape
I pasted the top line
After pasting the tape
Put this
The board is hard
After hardening
I can pull it to the other side
Because under the adhesion of the tape
The board can slide along the tape
It's a little more convenient
I can pull it to the other side
Then copy
Use another
Use the intelligent arrangement function at the upper right of the locator
Put it to the back
Here, the corresponding
Also put it under the line
I was on 3D
Probably find a certain position
Then adjust its length
After the top is done
This length is not very suitable
I changed this point a little
Because this point does not need to exist
So I re-adjust the position of this powder line
After the point is replaced, pay attention to re-adjust it
Because the nature of the line has been changed again
Then use the positioning ball to duplicate it to the right
Harden to speed up the simulation
Now I will use this lace fabric for it
This fabric has a larger texture
So you can adjust it a little bit
Name it lace 3
Reduce this lace fabric
Because the fabric is stretched in 3D
So it will be larger than the 2D fabric
It's normal
Then copy another fabric to give us this lace 4
I want to put it on the waist belt and the top
The fabric of the socks is on the salt
To give it a level
Level
Just rotate 90 degrees
Use the top of it
Use this pattern for the time being
But I will change another pattern later
Because I think this pattern is not very good
Then here
Let's change the pattern of this hanger
Use this cotton fabric of lace 2
The lace edge we used on the bra
Here I need to put this pattern
I choose all four sides
Go together to turn its sand line direction
Note that it is not the pattern direction on the right side
It is the sand line of the fabric itself
Zilv direction
Because the lace edge on our bra
The direction has been adjusted
So you can't adjust the pattern direction of the upper right corner anymore
Now I find this
This flower edge is not very good
So I changed it again
What I do first is
I'll put the top of the socks on this piece
This is the top of the socks
At last
Draw the line
I will make the top of the socks
I will have the middle part of the left and right sides
Just draw the line
Like I have a line
Like a line
You can also make the bottom of the top of the right and left sides
Like this
So, I made the bottom part of the right and left sides
I will make the top of the left side
The length is about 12mm
I made two internal lines in the position corresponding to the sewing line
Then adjust my sewing line
Put the strap and my internal line together
Because I made about 1cm of internal line down
So extend my strap by 1cm
Because now their layers are interspersed
So select all of them and set the layers of these four to 1
Then it will be directly simulated to the outer layer
Then turn off the layer
Now I will make a 1cm internal line in the heart part
To make a seam
Similar to a seam, a reverse seam effect
So I made a square board inside
After sewing, add it to the inside
Diagonally
Now we can throw the strap away
Like this
Okay
It's good
I'm done
If I do this, I'm done with the adoptive four
Next, I'm going to give him our chest
I will untie his bra
Unbutton, untie the fabric
Now this suit is done
Good
This is the whole set of this bra production
As for the back
It's for everyone
If you want to change the pose with the bra, you need to change the pose with the bra and move with the model.
Remember to check if the shoulder strap is fixed by adding a pin.
For the position of the shoulder strap, first you need to shape it to prevent it from deforming.
Then you need to add a few more points on the shoulder strap.
Put a few more points on the shoulder strap.
As long as the position of the shoulder strap does not move, the shape of the bra will not be large.
So if you can do these two points, you can change the pose.
Look at the effect you just saw.
It is actually the shape of the shoulder strap is fixed here.
It is not a fixed pin, but a false pin.
Of course, you can also use a fixed pin.
After the fixed pin is fixed, you need to set it.
Then you need to adjust it to the model's surface.
But I personally think that the false pin is better.
Because if the position is not set well, you can also use the edited false pin to adjust its position.
So it's set here.
You can see that it can change the pose with the model.
It can be more stable.
In addition, the shoulder strap of the shoulder strap is attached to the shoulder strap position of the virtual model.
And for the pants, it is better to have a shoulder strap.
You can use the shoulder strap to fix your back eyes.
It is attached to the position of the shoulder strap of the virtual model behind you.
Or you can make the roughness of the model's surface larger.
What does it mean?
Let me show you.
Open it and take a look.
Just click on the virtual model.
Then there is a moving friction coefficient on the digital editor.
Adjust its value to 0.6 or 0.8.
This can prevent the material from sliding on the surface of the model.
In this way, when you move, the waist and back will not have a big problem of sliding.
Does the virtual model have a function?
This virtual model is the virtual model of our CLO.
Then I just adjusted its size.
By pose model.
By pose model is the same model.
I just changed its hairstyle.
It is our own model.
For this model, you can buy the hairstyle online or find some hair materials.
Then tie it to the CLO model.
That's it.
How to tie it?
Before, we, Samantha, have been on a live broadcast.
I have taught you how to tie your own hair.
In fact, it is the same model.
Then change the posture.
Change the posture is very simple.
You just click this.
Google.
Just use the function of this IK point to adjust its posture.
You can adjust any posture you want.
Specifically, we have also been on a related live broadcast before.
You can see the previous live broadcast.
These are all things that I have done before.
You can go and see it again.
Is there any problem?
Did someone ask a question just now?
The size of the waist of the product.
Is it the size of the waist of the model?
Or the size of the pants?
The size of the pants is relatively small.
It is stretched.
The size of the model.
Here you can take a look at its waist.
The waist.
I made it 68 cm.
Are there any other questions?
Hurry up and hide my model.
Is there an audience in front of me?
Asked the finished product.
Externally.
Where is it?
Together internally and externally.
Closed.
Double-welded.
How to solve.
What is the internal and external control of the body?
Turn it over.
It's not a working one.
Just turn it over.
Add a line of internal and external control.
In short, internal and external control of the body is basically,
I, for example, draw a board.
Basically, it is solved by choosing the net grid tool.
Because the biggest problem with this kind of board is that it only has one board
There is no way to use the layer setting function to make it
Take an example
Make an internal line
I will sew it first
Then fold it
Make this board a little lighter
Not too tight
Then fold this
Split left and right
To rebuild your problem
I mess it up
Choose network grid symmetry
For example, this is the problem you may encounter sometimes
For example, I mess up here too
This one came out by itself
If your double-layer is folded
Double-layer appears
This situation is very simple
It's still this
I just messed it up with this
Still use it to fix it
Long press here
Choose network grid symmetry
Find the area where you have problems
Choose the area where you have problems
Then you can see after selection
You can see these green areas on the double-layer
Then you go to see
The white area should be outside
Now it's layered
That part of the white area went inside
Did you not frame when you selected
So at this time
Which places did you find that you didn't frame
You didn't choose here
So find this position
Directly frame this whole area
This is needed outside
So at this time
In the 3D window
In this green area at the same time
In this green area
Pull it out with this
Then you can solve it very quickly
Single-layer version of clothes
Oh my god
The temperature of the CPU is abnormal
Is there any problem
The computer crashed
The model who just posed
Do you want this material?
I'll share it with you
Because this is my own
I put it myself
It doesn't matter
Can share
I was also shocked
The temperature of the CPU is 97 degrees
How does the model move
You can search
We forgot
Before
The car driver
Have done a show live broadcast
I did that too
You can take a look at our
Previous live broadcast
You can search for keywords directly
Go show
You can find it
Does everyone have any questions?
Did you ask about the shirt version?
It's like what
What version of the question
This is
You can prepare your question
But
I don't know
I want to buy a question
Can you solve it in such a short time today?
You can try it
On our official website
The question channel
Or wechat background
Can also
Put your question
Describe
Because it seems that this question
May not be three words
Can explain to you
The button of the sleeve is easy to dock
If the button of your sleeve
There is a dock
Very simple
Take an example
What if you have a dock?
You just put your sleeve
Rearrange on the model's wrist
Arrange on the model's wrist
After arranging
Pay attention
Here
There should be a dock
If your sample is not long enough
There is no dock
For example, like this
What to do
In the attribute editor
Arrange inside
There is a
There is a frame
Adjust it to small
Adjust it to a certain dock
See it
There will definitely be a dock
There is a dock here
At this time
This dock
See if you need it
Usually it is pre-purchased
You see this is normal
If it is wrong
You can go to the direction of the package
Right-click on the board
This function
Turn in the direction of the package
In this way
It will reverse the package
Cancel
Rearrange
When you are ready
In this state
You put your corresponding button
Close your eyes
Add to it
Remember
Then simulate
It won't appear
That problem
What to do when the inner penetration problem that he just talked about appears when walking
Put your
Back again
Increase the thickness of the collision
Reduce the force
Through the thickness of the collision
The thickness of the collision
You can prevent a strong collision between the boards
To prevent this kind of problem from happening
Do you still have any questions?
No problem
That's it for us today
Thank you for your support
Then this year
This should be our year
This is the last live broadcast in 2021
Then
I wish you all
Wish you all
Happy New Year
Thank you all
Bye bye
The end
Thank you very much
Thank you for watching
If you like this video
Please share it
And subscribe to the channel
Thank you
See you next time
Good night
Bye, bye
Bye